We're now ready to wrap up our discussion of automatic memory management.
现在我们准备结束对自动内存管理的讨论。
And so I just want to make a few, high level points here. First of all,
所以我只想在这里提出几个高层次的观点。首先，
there's no question that automatic memory management is a great thing. It prevents very
毫无疑问，自动内存管理是一件很棒的事情。它可以防止非常
serious storage bugs, some of the most difficult bugs in programming, and when
严重的存储错误，编程中一些最困难的错误，以及何时
you're writing in the garbage collected language you really have just a
你在用垃圾收集的语言写东西，你真的只有一个
whole class of things you don't have to worry about and so it is certainly a more
你不用担心的所有事情，所以它肯定是一个更多的
productive way to program. So if, if your problem, your program is really a good fit
高效的编程方式。所以，如果你的问题是，你的程序真的很适合
for automatic memory management then you'd be crazy not to use a system that provided
对于自动内存管理，如果不使用提供以下功能的系统，那就太疯狂了
that kind of support. Now, the disadvantage of automatic memory management
那种支持。现在，自动内存管理的缺点是
is that it reduces programmer control. So you don't have control anymore
是它减少了程序员的控制。所以你不再有控制权了
over the layout of data and memory, and you don't have control over when the memory
控制数据和内存的布局，而您无法控制内存何时
is reallocated. So, you neither have control over where the data is in memory
是重新分配的。因此，您既无法控制数据在内存中的位置
and you have only a very limited amount of control over how much memory your
而且您只能非常有限地控制您的内存的大小
program is using, okay? And so if these two things don't matter, if your, if
程序在使用，好吗？所以如果这两件事都不重要，如果你，如果
your application is not extremely data intensive where the precisely out of data
您的应用程序的数据密集度不是很高，因为
memory and how much data is residing in memory is important then garbage collection
内存以及有多少数据驻留在内存中比垃圾收集更重要
will likely work very well. But there are applications particularly high end
可能会工作得很好。但是有一些应用特别高端
data processing and scientific applications which use a lot of data and need
使用大量数据和需求的数据处理和科学应用
to make very, very efficient use of the memory where garbage collection actually
为了非常、非常有效地使用内存，实际上垃圾收集
becomes too inefficient to do a good job and people in those domains still
变得效率太低，无法做好工作，这些领域的人仍然
use manual memory management. But there are some other issues. So, in real time applications
使用手动内存管理。但还有其他一些问题。因此，在实时应用程序中
the pauses can be problematic. So, if you have a program that
停顿可能会带来问题。所以，如果你有一个程序，
needs to meet guaranteed deadlines, many embedded systems that are interacting
需要满足保证的最后期限，许多正在交互的嵌入式系统
with the outside world say controlling dangerous machinery and things like that they
与外界打交道，比如说控制危险的机器之类的东西
have to have response times that are guaranteed to make sure that nothing terrible
必须有保证的响应时间，以确保不会有什么可怕的事情发生
happens. And, and you know, introducing a automatic memory management
时有发生。而且，你知道，引入了自动内存管理
system that might pause for arbitrary amounts of time you know, makes that a very
您知道，系统可能会暂停任意时间，这使得它非常
problematic things guaranty. So, you don't always see garbage selection used in
有问题的事情可以保证。因此，您并不总是看到垃圾选择在
real time applications. Although there has been a lot a progress in the last several
实时应用程序。尽管在过去的几年里已经取得了很大的进步
years on real time garbage collectors. Another issue for every programmer who uses
多年的实时垃圾收集器。对于每个使用
automatic memory management probably will have to face is the problem of memory
自动内存管理可能不得不面对的是内存问题
leaks. So, while automatic memory management prevents you from corrupting your
漏水了。因此，虽然自动内存管理可以防止您损坏您的
memory, it really doesn't prevent you from hanging on to too much data and possibly
内存，它真的不能阻止您保留太多数据，而且可能
affecting the performance of your program dramatically. So, memory leaks are
极大地影响程序的性能。因此，内存泄漏是
possible in garbage collected languages and I would say they are even likely. Said,
在垃圾收集语言中是可能的，我想说它们甚至是可能的。说,
you know, the fact that you're not as aware or not as forced to be aware of how
你知道，事实上你没有意识到或者没有被迫意识到
the memory is being used makes it easier to have memory leaks. And the kind
正在使用的内存更容易发生内存泄漏。而且是那种
of memory leak that you will have in say, a Java program is that you'll have some you
内存泄漏的可能性，比如说，Java程序就是您会有一些
know, some variable say x that points to some data structure and this data structure
知道吗，一些变量比如x指向某个数据结构和这个数据结构
is gigantic, okay? So lets say that this is the abstract syntax tree, in
是巨大的，好吗？假设这是抽象语法树，在
a compiler, alright? Now there may come a point in the computation where you don't need
一个编译器，好吗？现在，计算中可能会出现一个点，您不需要
the abstract syntax tree anymore. So let's say that we have converted to an intermediate
不再使用抽象语法树。所以让我们假设我们已经转换成一个中间体
language and from the abstract syntax tree and now all our processing
语言和抽象语法树，现在我们所有的处理
for the rest of the compilation is going t be on the intermediate language
因为睡觉的汇编将会在中间语言上进行
representation and generating code from that, we never go back and look at the abstract
表示并由此生成代码，我们再也不会回头看抽象
syntax tree again. Well, the compiler I mean, excuse me, the, the garbage
又是语法树。嗯，编译器我是说，打扰一下，垃圾
collector doesn't know that you are not going to use the abstract syntax tree
收集器不知道您不会使用抽象语法树
again in the future. And if you have a variable that's pointing to this gigantic
在未来还会有一次。如果你有一个变量指向这个巨大的
data structure even if you are not using it, it's gong to hang around and
数据结构，即使您不使用它，它也会继续存在
is going to be using up memory. And so the right thing to do is when you reach a point
将会耗尽内存。所以正确的做法是当你到达一个点的时候
in program where you are not going to use this data structure anymore is to assign
在您将不再使用此数据结构程序中，指定
x the null value. You want to assign x to null at that point and essentially
x空值。您希望在该点将x赋值为NULL，并且本质上
dropping this pointer to the data structure. And now the garbage collector,
将此指针放到数据结构中。现在是垃圾收集器，
whatever form it is, mark and sweeps, Stop and copy or reference counting
无论是什么形式，标记和清扫、停止并复制或引用计数
will be able to see that this is no longer reachable and will collect that
将能够看到这不再是可访问的，并将收集
big structure. And this is very, very common in, in production Java programs to
很大的结构。在生产Java程序中，这是非常、非常常见的
have these kinds of memory leaks where you just have pointers that you forgot about to
有这种类型的内存泄漏，您只是忘记了
data that you're no longer going to use. So as a whole, I have conveyed in the
您将不再使用的数据。所以作为一个整体，我在
last few lectures, garbage collection is a very important technique. Every programmer
上几节课，垃圾收集是一项非常重要的技术。每个程序员
should be aware of its benefits and costs and it's also very interesting aspect of programming
应该意识到它的好处和成本，这也是编程的一个非常有趣的方面
language implementation. There are much more advanced garbage collecting
语言实现。有更先进的垃圾收集技术
algorithms than we have discussed in these lectures and the primary dimensions along
算法，比我们在这些课程中讨论的算法和主要维度
which people have thought about improving garbage collection, that is making garbage
人们想过要改进垃圾收集，那就是制造垃圾
collection concurrent. That means allowing the program to continue to run while other
收款并发。这意味着允许程序在其他程序运行的同时继续运行
collection is happening. So the collector is working in the background actively while
正在进行收集。因此收集器在后台积极工作，同时
the program is running. Another thing that's very common actually in, in production
程序正在运行。另外一件事实际上在，在生产中是非常普遍的
collectors is to what's called a generational collector. And the basic idea
收藏家就是所谓的世代收藏家。它的基本理念是
here is that we don't want to keep going over lo oking at objects that are very
这就是我们不想一直看着那些非常重要的物体
long lived on every collection. So, collections happen very frequently and there
长寿地生活在每一个收藏品上。因此，收集非常频繁地发生在那里
will be some objects that just live for very long time, the big data structures
将是一些只存活很长时间的对象，即大数据结构
that hang around for most of the program. And once we have seen them, in
在节目的大部分时间里都挂着。一旦我们看到他们，在
a couple of collections we probably can assume that they're going to be around for
几个收藏品，我们大概可以假设它们将会在
a few more collections. And so in a generational collection sorry in a generational
再来几个收藏品。所以在代际集合中，抱歉在代际集合中
collector older objects, objects that have been around for a while
收集器较旧的对象，已存在一段时间的对象
are put in a seperate area and they're collected less frequently. And this just allows
被放在一个单独的区域，它们被收集的频率较低。而这正好允许
the collector to focus on the objects that are most likely to be garbage
收集器将重点放在最有可能是垃圾的对象上
which are the recently allocated objects. We already talked a little bit about Realtime.
它们是最近分配的对象。我们已经略微谈到了实时技术。
So there are collectors that try to bound the length or the, bound the length
所以有收集器试图限制长度或限制长度
of the maximum pause, the maximum interruption to the program. And finally parallel
在最大暂停中，是对程序的最大中断。最后是并行的
collectors. So collector systems where the garbage, there's actually several
收藏家。所以垃圾收集器系统，实际上有几个
garbage collectors running at the same time and somehow coordinating their actions.
垃圾收集器同时运行，并以某种方式协调它们的操作。